<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rs.xsl" ?>
<doc>
    <assembly>
        <name>Live Collabrative Text Editor</name>
        <version>1.0</version>
    </assembly>

    <requirements>

       <requirement name="F:Server_setpassword">
        <summary>
            Sets a password for the server to be connected to with. Preventing unauthorized use of the server.
        </summary>
       </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Server_modifyFileGroup">
        <summary>
          The server needs to be able to create an delete a filegoup in addition to setting a user for a newly created
          filegroup.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Server_modifyUsers">
        <summary>
          Allows removing and adding of users to the server. If a user is not on the list the only action they can
          do is request access. Until their access has been approved by an admin they can do anything. If a user is
          deleted they must not be the leader of any filegroup and if they are the groups need to be deleted or a
          new leader must be asigned to the filegroup.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Server_modifyUserRights">
        <summary>
          A user can be set as an admin only on the server side of the system. If a user is an admin then they 
          can modify filegroups and approve people to the server. This can only be done server side as there will
          only be one level of admin.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Server_confirmUser">
        <summary>
          Once a user sends a request, the request can be handled server side or remotely handled by an admin.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Admin_modifyFilegroup">
        <summary>
          This requirement is the same as "Server_modifyFileGroup". However, it must be able to do so remotely from a
          client.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Admin_modifyUser">
        <summary>
          This requirement is the same as "Server_modifyUsers". However, it must be able to do so remotely from a 
          client gui.
        </summary>
      </requirement>
      
      <requirement name="F:Admin_confirmUser">
        <summary>
          This requirement is the same as "Server_Confirm". However, it must be able to do so remotely from a client
          gui.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Client_connect">
        <summary>
          The user of the client gui must be able to connect to the server.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Client_login">
        <summary>
          Once connected the user must be able to login and logoff in addition to requesting access if it hasnt already
          been granted.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Client_connectFilegroup">
        <summary>
          The user of the client gui must be able to connect to a filegroup to have access to any files.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Client_sendText">
        <summary>
          Users can send text messages to the server where they will be distributed to everyone labeled as connected.
        </summary>
      </requirement>
      
      <requirement name="F:Client_receiveText">
        <summary>
          In addition to sending text, the user must able to receive and have messages displayed.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Client_openFile">
        <summary>
          Any connected user that is authenticated through the server and has access to a filegroup must be able to
          open a file in the document editor.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Client_closeFile">
        <summary>
          Once a file is open, the user must be able to close it.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Client_changeFile">
        <summary>
          If a file is not locked a user must be able to move, delete or rename the file.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:Client_create">
        <summary>
          Any connected user that is authenticated through the server and has access to a filegroup must be able to
          create a file from scratch.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:GUI_client">
        <summary>
          The client gui must be able to edit, open, delete, move, and create files. In addition it must be able to 
          perform all functions list above for "Client_"
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:GUI_client">
        <summary>
          The client gui must be able to handle all items list above under "Admin_" as a entity seperate from the 
          client gui.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="F:GUI_admin">
        <summary>
          The client gui must be able to edit, open, delete, move, and create files. In addition it must be able to
          perform all functions list above for "Client_"
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="C:Time">
        <summary>
          There is no oppurtunity to extend or modifiy the deadline in anyway, barring unforseen cirsumtances (meteor 
          destroying the world, second coming, etc)
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="C:Network">
        <summary>
          The network code needs to be able to handle input from many users and handle a network that is slow or unusable.
        </summary>
      </requirement>

      <requirement name="R:Syntactic highlighting">
        <summary>
          Text highlighting for C# will be implemented if time permits. However, the deadline is not worth missing 
          over colored text.
        </summary>
      </requirement>
    </requirements>


</doc>
